[
    {
        "front": "せんぱい\n「先輩」",
        "back": "senior colleague",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "こうはい\n「後輩」",
        "back": "junior colleague",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "しき\n「式」",
        "back": "ceremony",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ちょうどいい",
        "back": "suitable; just right",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "スーツ",
        "back": "suit",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ドレス",
        "back": "dress",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぜんぜん～ない",
        "back": "not ~ at all",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "きめる\n「決める」",
        "back": "to decide",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "（～が）きまる\n「決まる」",
        "back": "to be decided",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ショッピング",
        "back": "shopping",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "さがす\n「さがす」",
        "back": "to look for",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ゆびわ（アクセサリー）",
        "back": "ring (accessory)",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "Tシャツ",
        "back": "t-shirt",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "スカート",
        "back": "skirt",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "サンダル",
        "back": "sandals",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ぼうし",
        "back": "Hat, Cap",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "コート",
        "back": "coat",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ポケット",
        "back": "pocket",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "マフラー",
        "back": "scarf",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "てぶくろ\n「手袋」",
        "back": "gloves",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "セーター",
        "back": "sweater",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ズボン（パンツ）",
        "back": "trousers (pants)",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ブーツ",
        "back": "boots",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    },
    {
        "front": "したぎ\n「下着」",
        "back": "underwear",
        "chapter": "N4 C2"
    }
]
